Guide to the Fredericka Martin Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Photo Albums, circa 1937-1938
  - Green Photo Album, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_26ac6c922f702568031f661236a2a246)
- Series IV: Addendum (2012), 1936-1974
  - Briggs, Judson: Painting, "Girl With Necklace", undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - AMB: First Unit Landing At Le Havre, Jun 1, 1937 (Box OS006, Folder 1)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals -- Europe - En Route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals -- U.S., circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals - Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - At the Front: "Bringing the Wounded to the Rear, After the Battle", circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - At the Front: Soldiers Charging (Spanish Civil War), circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ayers, Frank and Anita, June 6, 1953; 1969; undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ayers, Frank - Holiday Card, circa 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Barsky, Dr. Edward; Rebecca Schulman, [Rodofo - Rudolph?], ["Sabateur & Agent ?"], circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bombed/Shelled Buildings: Valencia -- Group of Houses Destroyed by Italian Bombers, Oct 3, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cordoba, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fuhr (de Vries), Lini - Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Hospital: Unidentified Hospital Interior (Spain), circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Jake Cohen's Home, Jan 1, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee. Joaquin Gudino Flores, Miguel Negrin, Dr. Edward Barsky, Nickolai Zimenkov, Dr. Bedrich Syrovy, circa 1943 - 1944 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Luba [Luba Bresher?], undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Refugees (Spain), circa 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Reger, Muriel, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Taft, Anne and Helen Feinberg At Party, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Two Unidentified Men at Villa Paz (separated from Anne Taft correspondence, 1970), undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified Individuals (Spain), circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 22)